# lowrenmoore

## 👪 graphic + web designer 🐌



Lawren Moore is a unique graphic and web designer who believes that life is tasteless and chaotic without design. Her love and passion for music is what drives her to create and design and has been the engine that has driven her throughout her entire life of creativity. Her goal is to work amongst other creative individuals in a creative environment to expand and improve her own knowledge and skills.



# design skills

CSS/XHTML

Photoshop

Photography (manual+digital)

Flash

Typography

Layout/Ad Design/Print

Video Editing & Effects

Javascript, PHP/MySQL

# AE AI DW ID Lr Ps Fl E @

#### accomplishments/awards



'Graduation from GBC Graphic Design



GBC Portfolic Club



Typography
Award in
2nd year
Design Show



1st place MADD Ad Contest 2008



1st place Photography contest in Early Harvest

#### personal

Canadian. female. twenty one years-young.

music, photography, designing, reading, sleeping, tea, mangoes, the internet, anything and everything Japanese.

## recent works



The Box Tiger | Official Site Website created for a local, indie rock band, using flash, CSS/XHTML. Also part of design thesis.

Jan 2011 - April 2011



The Box Tiger | EP Cover Art Cover art created for a local indie rock band, using photoshop + indesign. May 2010

# education



George Brown College SCHOOL OF DESIGN

Graphic Design • Advertising 2008 - 2011 with honors

#### employment

#### Logistics Coordinator

Rose E. Dee Int'l LTD

Aug 2011 - Sept 2011

#### Merchandiser/Post Office Clerk

Shoppers Drug Mart (Woodbridge)

Feb 2009 - July 2011

#### Customer Experience Representative

Chapters (Indigo's) Book Store (Woodbridge)
Oct 2007 - Jan 2008

# languages



English
Conversational French
Basic Japanese
Basic Italian